{
    "1": {
      "topic": "mcq",
      "question": "Question: Which of the following are animals that do not respond to being pulled on by other animals?",
      "options": [
        "Animals that do not respond to being pulled on by other animals through",
        "1. insects",
        "2. snails",
        "3. dogs",
        "4. cows"
      ],
      "user_answer": ""
    },
    "2": {
      "topic": "mine",
      "question": "and four answers",
      "options": [
        "How do writers use conflict to develop characters",
        "1. To heighten emotion, situations or themes in the story.",
        "2. To create suspense in the story.",
        "3. To challenge the character's values or beliefs.",
        "4. To reveal deeper into the character's motivations or backstory."
      ],
      "user_answer": ""
    },
    "3": {
      "topic": "jacket",
      "question": "What would a coat made of wool be called?",
      "options": [
        "a. blanket jacket",
        "b. belfry jacket",
        "c. sinker jacket",
        "d. slope jacket",
        "e. pile jacket"
      ],
      "user_answer": "d. slope jacket"
    },
    "4": {
      "topic": "kite",
      "question": "Which is the correct principle applicable to a kite moving at high speed in high winds?",
      "options": [
        "a) The force of the wind on it is equivalent to the tension between the string and the kite.",
        "b) The force of the wind is equal to the weight of the kite.",
        "c) The force of the wind is equal to the tension of the string and the kite.",
        "d) The force of the wind is equal to the weight of the kite.",
        "e) The strength of the wind is not significant at extremely high speeds."
      ],
      "user_answer": "c) The force of the wind is equal to the tension of the string and the kite."
    },
    "5": {
      "topic": "one",
      "question": "answer",
      "options": [
        "Question: An orde with a rigid wall of core Oh no, we can't say it's a rigid wall of core",
        "Answer: nitrogen",
        "Distractors:",
        "1. hydrogen",
        "2. oxygen"
      ],
      "user_answer": "Distractors:"
    },
    "6": {
      "topic": "earth",
      "question": "\u2019s energy",
      "options": [
        "Its energy comes from sunlight, and oxygen, the elements that make up the planet."
      ],
      "user_answer": ""
    },
    "7": {
      "topic": "rotate",
      "question": "Question: When does a child need to be vaccinated against diphtheria?",
      "options": [
        "a. as soon as he turns 1 year old",
        "b. once in two weeks",
        "c. once in a month",
        "d. once every three months",
        "e. depending on the country and disease",
        "1. A toddler still gets diseases at the age of 1 so at least one dose of vaccine should be administered.",
        "2. With diphtheria, the vaccine is given once in two week intervals.",
        "3. In diphtheria, the vaccine we give is once in a month.",
        "4. In diphtheria, the vaccine is given once every three months.",
        "5. It depends on the country"
      ],
      "user_answer": ""
    },
    "8": {
      "topic": "disease",
      "question": "Question: What is the most common cause of premature ejaculation?",
      "options": [
        "A. Deprivation of oxygen",
        "B. Lack of blood flow",
        "C. Cell damage",
        "D. Prolonged stress"
      ],
      "user_answer": ""
    },
    "9": {
      "topic": "study",
      "question": "Question: During active cytomegalovirus replication, the virus stimulates human fibroblasts to produce",
      "options": [
        "a) RNA",
        "b) protein",
        "c) DNA",
        "d) none of these"
      ],
      "user_answer": "b) protein"
    },
    "10": {
      "topic": "work",
      "question": "Question: What can use atomic bombs to cool down a city?",
      "options": [
        "1. Hot air",
        "2. Heat generation",
        "3. Air distribution",
        "4. Frozen nitrogen"
      ],
      "user_answer": "3. Air distribution"
    },
    "11": {
      "topic": "science",
      "question": "quiz",
      "options": [
        "Question: A cluster is a type of lake?",
        "a) Crater",
        "b) Coral",
        "c) Marsh",
        "d) Pond",
        "e) Rainforest"
      ],
      "user_answer": ""
    },
    "12": {
      "topic": "physics",
      "question": "If you throw a heavy object with a very heavy force,",
      "options": [
        "the object is accelerated",
        "when it strikes the ground",
        "microgravity",
        "the object is not accelerated",
        "it moves through air with no force",
        "it is accelerated"
      ],
      "user_answer": "the object is not accelerated"
    },
    "13": {
      "topic": "cure",
      "question": ":",
      "options": [
        "Which of the following methods is considered a typically corrective method of treatment?",
        "a) behavior therapy",
        "b) birth control",
        "c) insulin therapy",
        "d) vaccination",
        "e) punishment"
      ],
      "user_answer": "c) insulin therapy"
    },
    "14": {
      "topic": "water",
      "question": "solubility",
      "options": [
        "Question: How many grams of carbon dioxide is dissolved per kilogram of water at 43 \u00b0C and 4.75 psia?",
        "Answer: 42.3 grams",
        "Distractors:",
        "1. 10 grams",
        "2. 15 grams",
        "3. 20 grams"
      ],
      "user_answer": "1. 10 grams"
    },
    "15": {
      "topic": "door",
      "question": "#2",
      "options": [
        "1. In the statement, abowl is without a bowl",
        "2.  bowl is without a bowl"
      ],
      "user_answer": ""
    },
    "16": {
      "topic": "food",
      "question": "circle",
      "options": [
        "Question: Who and where was the vegetarian dish invented?",
        "A. Durstenfeld",
        "B. Florence",
        "C. Sodex",
        "D. France"
      ],
      "user_answer": "C. Sodex"
    },
    "17": {
      "topic": "second",
      "question": "Taking the following text",
      "options": [
        "text = \"This text is in plain Latin\"",
        "<text>",
        "This text is in plain Latin.",
        "</text>",
        "import re",
        "transforms = re.compile(\"<text> {1}')",
        "text = transforms.substitute(\"<text> {0}\", \".\")",
        "print(text)",
        "Output:",
        "This text is in plain Latin.",
        "import re",
        "transforms = re.compile(\"<text> {1}'"
      ],
      "user_answer": ""
    },
    "18": {
      "topic": "code",
      "question": "about mutation",
      "options": [
        "take Int",
        "mutation {i: i - 1 }",
        "Ans: - i = i + 1;",
        "I: subtract 1",
        "I: subtract 1 plus 1",
        "I: i = i + 1;",
        "J: i++",
        "J: i++",
        "J: i++",
        "J: i++"
      ],
      "user_answer": "J: i++"
    },
    "19": {
      "topic": "huge",
      "question": "bodies of water",
      "options": [
        "1. Lake Superior",
        "2. North Atlantic Ocean",
        "3. Arctic Ocean",
        "4. Pacific Ocean",
        "1. Gobi desert",
        "2.,coxcomb-shaped lake",
        "3., hot-spot",
        "4., field of acid"
      ],
      "user_answer": "4. Pacific Ocean"
    }
  }